## EDUARDO TADASHI MORI

#### MATHEMATICIAN -DATA SCIENTIST



São Paulo, SP - Brazil



+55 11 997011345



tadashimori.br@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/tadashi-mori/



github.com/tadashiorigami

medium.com/@tadashi-mori

## PROFILE

Mathematician with experience in process optimization, programming, and team management. Certified data scientist professional.

Supervised the project and execution of industrial processes, working with multidisciplinary and multicultural teams. Highly logic-driven, self-driven, with a strong problem-solving mindset and unparalleled work ethic.

## SKILLS

- English
- Japanese
- Python / Numpy / Tensorflow / SKLearn/ Pandas / Jupyter / SQL
- Word / Excel / PowerPoint
- AWS Sagemaker / S3 / Cloud9
- Statistical inference / Time series

## **PROJECTS**

#### ADAPTIVE DECISION TREE

Personal project of a customized decision tree to maximize profits, classifying the data using entropy in the early nodes and profit gain close to the leaves. • Article Library

#### CUSTOM RANDOM FOREST

Tree ensamble using the adaptive decision tree, maximizing profits instead of the usual performance metrics. Article

## COURSES

- Data scientist professional -<u>Datacamp</u>
- Machine Learning Specialization -Coursera
- Practical Data Science on the AWS Cloud - Coursera
- Extreme Gradient Boosting with XGBoost - DataCamp

# EXPERIENCE

### MECHANICAL PROJECT DESIGNER

Termix Climatização Ind. e Com., Diadema/SP 2017 - 2021

- Process optimizations using Python, LISP and PLC.
- Storage optimization and control over website in Ruby on Rails

#### STOCK ANALYST

Banco Fator, São Paulo 2010 - 2011

- Spreadsheet automation with VB and SQL.
- · Stock analysis.

#### **YOUTUBER**

Youtube 2008 - 2021

- · Website programming in Ruby on Rails
- Al origami generator development

## **EDUCATION**

### **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE: MATHEMATICS**

Universidade de São Paulo, SP 2007 - 2014